[{"answer": "Well, I don't -- I don't actually know him.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "But what do you think of him personally?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, I actually don't like playing the race card on either side.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "When you see the charge of potential racism in the Herman Cain case, people saying that people are only going after him because he's a black conservative, do you think that holds any merit?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think you can read anything in at this point.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "What can you read into this from your experience?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Which of the candidates do you find yourself agreeing with most on their policy statements?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "No, I certainly don't get itchy fingers about throwing my own hat in the ring.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Do you think maybe you should throw your hat in the ring, albeit, belatedly?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Let's turn to your book.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "And so, the important thing to look for in candidates is what do they stand for, what are their principles, do they understand the unique character of the United States, and its unique role in the world?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there was the relief that I finally finished the writing, which, as you know, can be quite trying.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What did you conclude about that period in your life?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Let's start over.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "How have I done there?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Object of affection?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, revolutions are not pretty, and there are any number of circumstances in which the tyrant who stays too long and refuses to leave and when fear breaks down, and on behalf of his people, and the tables are turned, those ends are often very violent.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, the circumstances were fundamentally different, and the times were fundamentally different.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Do you look at what's happened to Barack and Gadhafi, and slightly regret the way you helped the administration go about Iraq?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I'm really a policy person.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Is that -- is that a total lifetime pass, or could you see yourself tempted back?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Piers, that's a no.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "You're not entirely ruling it out?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Well, I actually had a couple of people with me, traveling with me -- one of whom had worked with me at the State Department.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Who was the first person you told when you heard the news?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, of course, it was a wonderful experience, and it was a very high honor, as I said.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "So, I guess mixed feelings?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Well, clearly, associating the United States of America firmly with the freedom agenda in the Middle East after 60 years of trying to trade democracy for stability and getting neither, I'm very proud of that speech in Cairo in June of 2005 that set a different tone based on President Bush's second inaugural.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "And very quickly, if I was to pin you down and say your biggest triumph in the eight years and your biggest regret, what would you say?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "LLIOT ACKERMAN, COO, AMERICANS ELECT: I think you hit it right on the head.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Is that in a nutshell where we are with this?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Coming to your show today, it's already happening.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Are you going to end up come election with all the states allowing this or not?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "What's so interesting about it the Americans Elect platform gives the American people the opportunity to select leaders from business, from government, people who have expressed leadership roughly the previous 44 presidents have.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Do you need to have that kind of powerful figurehead for this to really work?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, we've had over 3,000 donors up until this point.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Who's funding al this?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "CKERMAN: Well, it's already a serious caper.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "If they're watching us and if they want to get involved in your caper, as it is at the moment, may become a more serious caper, where do they go?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "I mea, he's sort of a part of American history, isn't he?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "AYNE: He was -- he was very similar in a lot of ways.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What was he like when the door closed?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "He was very good with a gun.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Was he actually any good with a gun?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "AYNE: You know, it was -- it's always a strange time for young men when they're at that age.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "What were your recollections of that time in your life?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I don't know if there is.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What's the biggest misconception, do you think, of your father?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Piers, we're all shaking our heads.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "What would he have made of the modern political state and financial state of the America?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "He'd be upset.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Imagine he would have been pretty furious, wouldn't he?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Well, mine changes all the time, because, you know, I'm 49 now.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What's been your favorite movie of your father's -- if you could actually watch one again?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if there is another actor who's had the opportunity to, you know, create a space for themselves like John Wayne was able to.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "It is interesting, isn't it?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "AYNE: No, I can't.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Can you do a John Wayne?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if I would do it on national television.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "You never tried it?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I call that bold talk for a one-eyed fat man.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Which will it be?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Winning the Oscar for best actor?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Yes, because it's the ultimate in the profession, isn't it?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Always on the move.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "A well- traveled man, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "This is the Congressional Gold Medal and it's the highest civilian award.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "What is this one?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "This is from the \"Green Berets.\"", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Which movie is that from?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "I have my suspicions about the \"Green Beret.\"", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Who were people paying this kind of money?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Well, there was an individual who came out who is a former Special Forces, and he had done well, and I have a feeling that he may have bought that to put it in one of the Special Forces museums.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What are they?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "\"Horse Soldiers,\" \"She Wore a Yellow Ribbon\" and \"The Undefeated (ph).\"", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Which movie is that from?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Well, these are custom made.", "docId": "111106pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "What size?", "qSentId": 584}]